<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>K-Modes on Kevin Angotti</title>
    <link>https://kangotti.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/tags/k-modes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in K-Modes on Kevin Angotti</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 11:25:05 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kangotti.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/tags/k-modes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Science Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://kangotti.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kangotti.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my Data Science Portfolio. My passion is to understand better the interactions data science has in different industries. The conservation-restoration world and sports market are just two of the areas I am interested in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 9: Data Science Project 2</title>
      <link>https://kangotti.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/post/project-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kangotti.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/post/project-9/</guid>
      <description>When a person is looking to build their idea or business, one place they can turn is Kickstarter.com. This site allows for one to open a campaign to search for investors to back their idea. The Kickstarter site explains that the beginning stage of a campaign is the busiest time, and you can expect the first few days to be jam-packed as you will need to spread the word on your campaign, answer questions from potential backers and rally all your social media networks in order to reach your fundraising goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 8: Data Science Project 1</title>
      <link>https://kangotti.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/post/project-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kangotti.github.io/Data_Science_Portfolio/post/project-8/</guid>
      <description>Travel is a billion-dollar industry, and the hotel or lodging sector takes a large portion of the revenue. Airbnb has quickly become a staple in the travel sector. With their bookable locations in just about every travel destination worldwide, you can easily see why they have become so successful. This project looks to finding ways a customer can locate the best host to book based on location and affordability. One of the main goals was to determine if a plugin or application could be created to help make future Airbnb bookings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
